Now we have the reading
of the law.
Found in Exodus, the 20th chapter,
verses 1 through 17.
Okay, go ahead.
>> God spoke all these words, saying,
"I am the Lord thy God, which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt,
out of the house of bondage.
Thou shalt have no other gods before me.
Thou shalt not make unto thee any graven
image,
or any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above, or that is in the earth
beneath, or that is in the water under
the earth.
Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them,
nor serve them.
For I the Lord thy God am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me,
and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain.
For the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain.
Remember the sabbath day to keep it
holy.
Six days shalt thou labor and do thy
work.
But the seventh day is the sabbath of
the Lord thy God.
In it thou shalt not do any work,
thou, nor thy son, nor thy daughter, nor
thy man servant, nor thy maid servant,
nor thy cattle, nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates.
For in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth,
the sea, and all that in them is, and
rested the seventh day.
Wherefore the Lord blessed the sabbath
day, and hallowed it.
Honor thy father and
that thy days may be long upon the land
which the Lord thy God giveth thee.
Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not
commit adultery.
Thou shalt not steal. Thou shalt not
bear false witness against thy neighbor.
Thou shalt not covet thy neighbor's
house. Thou shalt not covet thy
neighbor's wife,
nor his man servant, nor his maid
servant, nor his ox, nor his ass, nor
anything that is thy neighbor's.
>> Now, let's go into Ecclesiastes, the
12th chapter.
Read verses 13 and 14.
Read them when you get there.
>> Let us hear the conclusion of the whole
matter.
Fear God and keep his commandments, for
this is the whole duty of man.
For God shall bring every work in the
judgment, every secret thing, whether it
be good or whether it be
>> Now, let's go into Revelation, chapter
22.
We're going to read verses 14
and 15.
So, read them when you get there.
>> Blessed are they that do his
commandments, that they may have right
to the tree of life, and may enter into
the gates into the city.
But without are dogs,
sorcerers, whoremongers, murderers, and
idolaters, and whosoever loveth it and
maketh a lie.
>> So, we're going to thank God for the
reading of the law.
Good afternoon, and as always, it is
good to stand before you on the Lord's
Sabbath day.
Hello, sisters and brothers.
This is the lesson I
together through the grace of God a long
time ago
because
I look at all of the people that call on
the name of Jesus
under all kind of faith and all kind of
denomination.
But when you listen to them after they
get through calling the name,
nothing
points toward him.
And so the Lord put it on my mind and
called to put the title of this lesson
Jesus
the unknown God.
Jesus the unknown God. You even have
religions saying that Jesus is son of
God, but he is not God.
But we're going to look at this, sister
and brother,
because nobody knows who Jesus is.
Well, brother brother Brewer, I know who
he is. Do you?
By the time we get through this lesson,
then you will answer your own question.
We're going to start this
in Acts the 17th chapter.
Because
when it get down to the Bible, sister
and brother, a lot of people talk about
the Bible, but don't don't nobody read
the Bible.
Now, you go to school all your life
so you can make money.
Then you go to extended school so you
can make more money.
But you don't want to spend any time
reading the word that's going to get you
eternal life on the good side of the
kingdom.
An average person don't understand that
the kingdom is God's. Satan ain't got no
kingdom. Why should a god give a
rebellious angel a domain?
He don't have no kingdom. kingdom is
God.
So now, God have two sides of the
kingdom. The good side when the people
is
are your children of God and you become
God, and the bad side of the people in
the lake of fire.
But either way it go, I want you to
understand one thing.
If you was born, you're going to live
forever.
But it is up to you now where you going
to live at.
Because the Lord put it in your hand.
But we're going to find out about this
unknown God, because don't nobody know
about Jesus. Everybody know Jesus this,
Jesus that.
We're going to see.
Acts 17th chapter.
And we're going to start at verse 15.
Acts 17 and 15.
Okay, go ahead.
>> And they that conducted Paul brought him
into Athens.
And receiving a commandment unto Silas
and Timotheus for them to come to him
with all speed, they departed.
>> Go ahead.
>> Now while Paul waited for them at
Athens, his spirit was stirred in him
when he saw the city wholly given to
idolatry.
>> Now it's
that happened to any servant of man,
servant of God, brother.
Sister or brother that have the truth
and you know the truth.
And you're in a place where all you hear
is idolatry.
And false to it. All of a sudden your
spirit gets stirred up in you, and
before you know it, you're preaching to
everybody.
Go ahead and read.
>> Therefore,
disputed he in the synagogues with the
Jews and with the devout persons, and in
the market daily with them that met with
him.
>> Go ahead.
>> Then certain philosophers
of the Epicureans and of the Stoics
encountered him, and some said, "What
will this babbler say?" Others, some, he
seemed to be a setter for forth of a
strange god because he preached into
them Jesus and the resurrection.
>> So, now you got these
These are Greeks
groups and Greeks organization that Paul
was dealing with in Athens, sisters and
brothers.
And everybody think that the Greeks have
all kind of knowledge.
And so you got these groups, they
started and Paul was disputing with all
of these. Now they say, "Well, look
here. This guy here seem to be setting
forth a strange god."
Because he spoke of Jesus and the
resurrection. Now I want you to
understand this.
These Greeks were Gentiles.
They had nothing They knew nothing about
Jesus.
Therefore, they cannot be the original
Christians, sisters and brothers.
This is what people don't understand.
They knew nothing. They didn't even know
the name and they had no idea about the
resurrection.
Skip down to verse 22.
Verse 22 and go ahead.
>> Then Paul stood in the midst of Mars'
Hill and said, "Ye men of Athens, I
perceive that in all things ye are too
superstitious."
>> Now understand Mars' Hill because we
used to have one here.
They used to call be called Washington
Park.
Every religion on the planet was out
there
pushing their god. So now
Paul stood up
and he said, "I see that the you you
Greeks here in Athens
you're suspicious of everything."
Go ahead and read.
>> 23. For as I passed by, behold your
devotions, I found an altar with this
inscription to the unknown God whom
therefore you ignorantly worship, him I
declare unto you.
>> He says, "I even saw you have a
inscription, a plaque out there with the
name the unknown God."
How you going to worship somebody a God
that you don't know nothing about?
But Paul said, "Him I'm going to declare
unto you."
And that's what we going to do today.
We're going to point out this unknown
God because every person when they think
God, they got it all messed up.
Some people got three in the Godhead.
They don't know who it is you know like
one religion say
you know
that you got three. Like a brother
called here one time argue with me about
God the Holy Ghost.
I said, "You can't even read that in the
book."
Then you turn around and you tell me
about God the Son.
Cuz God was the father and
as an individual rather, God was the
father in creation.
He He is the son in redemption and now
he's the Holy Ghost in the church, but
ain't but one.
Had one person preacher pushing it so
hard until I couldn't hold myself back.
I had to bake a cake for it.
I titled the lesson God.
Is it
more than one or just one that talks to
himself?
Because he is unknown sisters and
brothers. Unknown.
Now let's go into St. John
the first chapter.
John chapter 1.
We're going to read one verse.
Verse 18.
John chapter 1
and verse 18.
Okay, read it.
>> No man have seen God at any time.
>> Uh-huh.
>> The only begotten son, which is in the
bosom of the Father, he have declared
him.
>> He said, "Now, no man have seen God at
any time."
No man. So, let's go and see something
that look like it's contradictory.
Let's go into Exodus the 24th chapter.
Exodus chapter 24.
That's why when people come to the
Israel of God, it's just like
they're in constant state
of shock.
Because the stuff they hear when you
come here, if you stick here long
enough, you're going to hear stuff that
you didn't even know was in the Bible.
In fact, you're going to start looking
at your Bible seeing if you know,
you know, Brother Bowie or either
whoever whoever you teach you that day,
he must be teaching from some strange
book.
That's the one you got. That's why I
wanted to encourage everybody to bring
their own Bible.
But it said, "No man have seen God at
any time."
That's a That Any time covers all time,
don't it?
>> That's right.
>> So, let's see what we have here.
Exodus 24 and verse 1. Go ahead and
read.
>> And he said unto Moses, "Come up into
the Lord, thou and Nadab and Abihu, and
70 of the elders of Israel, and worship
you a fall."
>> Now, this is what God said. So, let's
see what happened. Skip down to verse 9.
Verse 9.
And go ahead.
>> Then went up Moses and Aaron, Nadab and
Abihu, and 70 of the elders of Israel
>> Uh-huh.
>> and they saw the God of Israel.
>> what?
>> The God of Israel.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> And there was under his feet as it were,
a paved work of a sapphire stone, or as
it were, the body of heaven in its
clearness.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And upon the nobles of the children of
Israel, he laid not his hand.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Also, they saw God and did eat and
drink.
>> So, now we have a look like a
contradictory here, don't we?
We have one saying, "Nobody man has seen
God." Now, we see 74 elders saw God.
And we find ourselves something else,
too.
That this God had feet.
He had hands.
But, I heard it years ago on the TV, on
the radio program, when they were trying
to talk about God, a woman come on and
say, "God don't have no form."
I called in and said, "If that's the
case, then how is it that we are made in
his image?"
So, now
24 elders saw God.
So, the question now is
who
was that God?
Let's go back to St. John, the fifth
chapter.
We're going to run him down.
St. John, chapter five, because if
people really knew
Jesus
you wouldn't have all these people
trying to get rid of the commandments.
Do away with the dietary law.
Tell males that they don't have to be
circumcised.
When I hear that kind of conversation, I
know you don't You don't know God. You
just calling on a name, sisters and
brothers.
You're wasting your time
and whoever sitting there looking at
you, you're wasting their time.
And these guys get paid well.
For For telling folk laws.
St. John 5
St. John 5 and we're going to start at
verse 33. This is Jesus letting these
people know that look, I I don't need uh
John to
uh uh uh no man to testify me.
Verse 33, 5 and 33. St. John 5 and verse
33.
Okay, go ahead.
>> Ye sent unto John and he bare witness
unto the truth.
>> Now, John bare witness of the truth, but
Jesus letting you know I don't need
John. Skip down to verse 36. Verse 36
and go ahead.
>> But I have greater witnesses than that
of John.
>> Go ahead.
>> For the work which the Father have given
me to finish
>> Uh-huh.
>> the same works that I do
>> Now, he said my works testify me. Go
ahead and read.
>> bare witness of me that the Father have
sent me.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the Father himself which have sent
me
me, go ahead.
>> have borne witness of me.
>> Go ahead.
>> Ye have neither heard his voice at any
time nor seen his shape.
>> Whoa.
What does that just tell us?
That the God
Lord God of Israel that the 74 elders
saw was not the Father.
People think that Jesus started with
Mary.
So now, if he said no man have seen the
Father at any time or heard the Father's
heard his voice or seen his shape at any
time
then either we have a great
contradictory or we better find us
another God.
So let's see if we can find us one.
Let's go into 1 Corinthians the 10th
chapter.
This is how you find out about stuff,
sisters and brothers. You come to
Israel, you know, like a person called
to me, "Well, when do y'all have Bible
study? I said, "Every Sabbath day."
You ready? Yeah, we're taking you to
school.
1 Corinthians the 10th chapter.
Now,
we see that no man have seen the Father.
So, who's left?
1 Corinthians 10 and verse 1. Go ahead
and read it.
>> Moreover, brethren,
I would not that you should be ignorant
how that all our fathers were under the
cloud,
all passed through the sea,
>> Uh-huh.
>> and were all baptized into the Moses in
the cloud and in the sea.
>> He said, "I don't want you to be
ignorant of this." Because this time
when Israel come out of Egypt and come
through the Red Sea. Go ahead and read.
>> And did not And did all eat the same
spiritual meat,
>> And they all eat ate the same spiritual
meat. Go ahead and read.
>> And did all drink the same spiritual
drink.
>> Go ahead.
>> For they drank of that spiritual rock
that followed them.
>> And who was that?
>> And that rock was Christ.
>> Oh, so it was Jesus back there in with
Moses them, wasn't it?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Jesus is the one that directed the the
sent them evil angels in Egypt and
destroyed it.
He's the one
that separated the sea.
But everybody think that that
was the Father.
Sisters and brothers,
it was Jesus that's the one that was in
the cloud in the daytime and it was him
in the pillar of fire at nighttime. If
you ain't seen the Father, then who's
left? God the Holy Ghost?
I challenge people all the time. I said,
"Go in there one time. me one time in
the Bible where it say
God the Holy Ghost."
Let's go in Exodus the 13th chapter.
Exodus 13th chapter.
Because all
of this inner reaction
that Israel had with God,
it wasn't the Father.
So, who else was left? I don't I always
saying all the time, when you throw out
everything that is not,
whatever is whatever is left, that's it.
Exodus 13.
And we're going to start reading at
verse 17. Exodus 13.
verse 17.
Okay, go ahead.
>> And it came to pass, when Pharaoh had
let the people go,
that God led them not through the way
of the land of the Philistines.
>> Go ahead.
>> Although that was near, for God said,
"Lest peradventure the people repent,
and they see war, and they return to
Egypt."
>> See it? See
it was shorter by going directly
standing on land, but the Lord knew that
this people ain't got no uh uh
uh
appetite for war, so it took took them
another way. What verse was that?
>> We are 18.
>> Go ahead.
>> But God led the people about through the
way of the wilderness of the Red Sea.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And the children of Israel went up
harnessed out of the land of Egypt.
>> Go ahead.
>> And Moses took the bones of Joseph with
him, for he had straightly sworn to the
children of Israel, saying,
"God will surely visit you, and you
shall carry my bones away hence with
you."
>> Now, skip down to verse 21 and you
Go ahead.
>> And the Lord went before them by day in
a pillar of a cloud to lead them the way
and by night in a pillar of fire to give
them light to go by the day and night.
>> Go ahead.
>> And he took not away the pillar of the
cloud by day nor the pillar of fire by
night from before the people.
>> So now
now we know who was in the cloud, don't
we?
It wasn't the father.
It was Jesus, sisters and brothers.
So Jesus
being God
had to become a flesh and blood man
to save
man
from his own suicide.
So let's look at this transformation.
See, people can't don't understand
that the one that came
and was named Jesus
was the one that did everything.
We going to show it to you.
So he had to become flesh to save this
man. Now let's look at this
transformation.
Let's go into Isaiah
chapter 48. Isaiah chapter 48. Because
that's what we do here at the Israel of
God, sisters and brothers. We teach the
word of God. Skip all this ideology.
And and and about man. Like I say all
the time, I don't have no dog in this
fight. I'm going to teach you this book.
Now if you don't want it, you can walk.
But I guarantee you going to be sorry
later.
We got too many people in here that's
smarter than God.
But in Israel of God
we know that our righteousness is just
like a filthy rag.
So, we going to wait on the Lord.
Isaiah 48
and we're going to start reading
at verse 12. Isaiah 48
and we're going to start reading at
verse 12.
Okay, go ahead.
>> Hark and hear me, O Jacob and Israel,
my called,
I am he;
I am the first, and I also am the last.
>> See, people read this, but they don't
understand what that mean.
I'm the first God that you will deal
with you that will deal with you
and the last God that you will
deal with.
Why? It's because when we see the
Father, sister and brother, there will
be no species that called man.
There will be no flesh and blood.
There won't even be death.
That's why it said,
I'm Alpha and Omega. I am the first and
the last. Go ahead and read.
>> My hand also have laid the foundation of
the earth.
>> My hand have laid the foundation of the
earth. Go ahead.
>> And my right hand has spanned the
heaven.
heaven. Go ahead and read.
>> When I call them to them, they stand up
together.
>> Now, this is the God talking here.
>> Yes.
>> What else did he say? Skip down to verse
16. Verse 16 and go ahead.
>> Come you near to me.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Hear ye.
>> Go ahead.
>> I have not spoken in secret from the
beginning.
>> He said, "I have not spoken in secret
from the beginning." The Lord have not
held nothing back from man. You go ahead
and read.
>> From the time that it was,
>> Uh-huh.
>> there am I.
>> From the time that it was, there was I.
There am I.
A present. Go ahead and read.
>> And now the Lord God and his spirit has
sent me.
>> Wait a minute.
This guy laid the foundation of earth.
His right hand spanned the heavens.
Now you going to tell me that somebody
sent him? Yes.
The one that became the father. He
wasn't the father in the beginning.
But he was sent. And he came by way of a
woman, sisters and brothers.
God set an order of creation.
And he set it so that everybody was was
God took man's rib and made the woman.
He set it so that everybody from that
day on, if they come into existence,
they had to come by way of a woman.
He didn't break his own protocol. And
this is what people got to understand.
God could have just turned flesh and
blew it up.
Uh-uh.
He brought He came by way of the
protocol that's been set. That's why
Adam told Eve,
"I'm going to name you Eve because you
are the mother of all living. If you
didn't come by way of Eve, you do not
exist. Y'all understand?"
Evening and the morning.
Evening come first.
So he said, "In order for him to do
that, he had to become
flesh."
And let's see you
how he did that. Let's back up to
Isaiah, the seventh chapter.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Cuz nobody want to read, but everybody
smart.
And we're going to start at verse 10.
Isaiah 7
and 10.
and we're going to start reading at
verse 10.
Okay, go ahead.
>> Moreover, the Lord spake again unto
Ahaz, saying,
>> Uh-huh.
>> Ask thee a sign of the Lord thy God;
ask it either in the depth, or in the
height above.
>> He said, "I want you to ask a sign.
Whatever sign you ask, I'm going to do
it."
But what did Ahaz say? Go ahead and
read.
>> But Ahaz said, I will not ask, neither
will I tempt the Lord.
>> Go ahead.
>> And he said, Hear ye now, O house of
David, is it a small thing for you to
weary men, but will you weary my God
also?
>> Go ahead.
>> Therefore the Lord himself shall give
you a sign.
>> Therefore the Lord who?
>> Himself.
>> Himself going to give you a sign. He
ain't going to send no angel to do this.
He going to do this himself.
Go ahead.
>> Behold, a virgin shall conceive,
>> Uh-huh.
>> and bear a son, and shall call his name
Immanuel.
>> Now,
all of my Hebrew brothers
show on the word, you know, a virgin.
You know, a virgin, you know, you mean
Look, he had a daddy. The book said a
virgin. What is a virgin in anybody's
language?
A woman that has never laid with a man.
Isn't that correct?
>> That's right.
>> Virgin shall conceive, and bear a son,
and shall be and shall call his name
Immanuel.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Well, I thought his name was Jesus. Wait
a minute. Let's before we jump to
conclusion, let's see what Immanuel is
talking about.
So let's go into Matthew, the first
chapter.
We are just reading books, sisters and
brothers.
>> Yes, sir.
>> But when you line the scriptures up
like the Lord want us to,
they speak for themselves.
You don't need no guy like me to explain
what God wants you to understand?
God like me is supposed to direct you in
this book. So, the book will show you
what God wants you to understand.
>> That's it, brother. That's it.
>> That's why I never could understand why
people run around calling people
boyites.
Did I write this book?
So, how can you be a boyite if you quote
it and understand it?
Matthew chapter 1 and we're going to
start reading at verse 18.
Matthew chapter 1 and verse 18.
1 and 18.
Okay, go ahead.
>> Now, the birth of Jesus Christ was on
this wise:
When as his mother was espoused to
Joseph, before they came together, she
was found with child of the Holy Ghost.
>> Now, before her and Joseph laid
together,
she was found pregnant.
Said with the child of the Holy Ghost.
Go ahead and read.
>> Then Joseph her husband being a just
man, and not willing to make her a
public example, was minded to put her
away privately.
>> Now, we're going to learn something on
our way. We're learning something.
You got Hebrews running around here
telling me when you lay a woman with a
woman, she become your wife.
Mary was Joseph's wife and he hadn't
touched her.
It is the vows that make you
husband and wife.
It's all that simple.
So, he's going to put her away privately
cuz he's a just man. But, go ahead and
read.
>> But, while he thought on these things,
behold, an angel of the Lord appeared to
him in a dream, saying, "Joseph,
>> Uh-huh.
>> thou son of David, fear not to take to
thee Mary thy wife:
>> Go Go
>> for that which is conceived in her is of
the Holy Ghost.
>> Now, what did he call Mary, now, what?
>> Wife.
>> Because this
which is conceived in her
is by way of the Holy Spirit. The ghost
ain't nothing but a slang for spirit. I
wish they had never even come up with
the word.
Go ahead and read.
>> And she being She shall bring forth a
son
and shall call his name Jesus.
>> Go ahead.
>> And he shall
save his people from their sins.
>> So, she's going to bear with a son
called name Jesus, and he's going to
save the people from their sins. Go
ahead and read.
>> Now, all this was done that it might be
fulfilled which was spoken by the Lord
by the prophet saying,
>> Go ahead.
>> Behold, a virgin shall be with child and
shall bring forth a son, and they shall
call his name Emmanuel.
>> Now, you get my Hebrew brothers, they
tell me they old testament, they don't
new testament don't mean.
WHAT DID
THIS JUST QUOTE?
>> ISAIAH.
>> She's going to conceive and have a son
and she's going to call his name
Emmanuel. Let's see what that mean. Go
ahead and read.
>> Which being interpreted is, God with us.
>> When Jesus came in the flesh, wasn't God
with us?
>> Yes, he was.
>> So, there ain't no conflict with the
name of Jesus and Emmanuel because both
of them mean different things.
Jesus is savior. Emmanuel God with us.
>> That's right.
>> For this is God that laid the foundation
of the earth. This is the God that
expanded the heavens
with his right hand.
>> Yes, sir.
>> And then he came in the flesh. When he
did, God was with us.
Let's go into 1 Timothy
the third chapter.
The people like to discuss stuff like
this and talk about Why you going to
talk about something
when you can just turn over and read it
and then it tell you what it mean.
>> Right.
>> But we like to talk about stuff so we
can show how smart we are.
Then when somebody open the book and
read it on you, now that let you know
how dumb you are.
First Timothy
third chapter
and we're going to start We're going to
read one verse.
First Timothy 3
and 16.
3 and 16.
Okay, read it.
>> And without controversy
great is the mystery of godliness.
>> It is great is the mystery of godliness.
Go ahead and read.
>> God was manifested in the flesh
>> Who was?
>> God.
>> Go ahead.
>> Justified in the spirit
>> Uh-huh.
>> seen of angels
>> Go ahead.
>> preached unto the Gentiles
>> Now that's the part I don't remember
seeing him do. But keep reading.
>> Believed on in the world
>> Believed on in the world? Go ahead.
>> and received up in the glory.
>> And went back to where he came from when
he had done his job.
God was manifested in the flesh. That
mean God came in the flesh, didn't it?
>> Yes, sir.
>> He was revealed in the flesh.
But nevertheless, he was God, sister and
brother.
>> Yes.
>> And once he came and did what he wanted
to do, he
went back to where he came from.
>> Yes.
>> Now let's back up to St. John the first
chapter.
St. John chapter 1
because we're just letting the book
teach you now, sister and brother.
All I am is the one that's directing you
to the scripture.
So how you going to go out of here
telling about Billy said?
And you're reading it with your own
eye.
And you understand everything that you
read.
That's why they come up with all these
new version of Bible. Tell me you know
what this modern day English. Look, you
understand everything you read.
You get at these these these new
translation come up, they don't just
translate,
they remove stuff.
And they add stuff to make that false
doctrine that they call the word of God
legitimate.
When the book said thou, we know it's
talking about you.
Oh, that's simple.
One and one, verse one. Go ahead and
read.
>> In the beginning was the word.
>> In the beginning was the word. That was
the spokesman assistant, brother.
Cuz he ain't We read that you ain't
never heard the father's voice, right?
So, in the beginning was the word. Go
ahead and read.
>> And the word was with God.
>> was with God.
>> And the word was God.
>> And the word was God. Now, how can you
sit in front of a preacher that's going
to tell you that they even one?
What does with mean?
That let me know that people that are
believe a lie
want to believe a lie.
Cuz all you got to do is read this book.
In the beginning was the word, the word
was with God, and the word was God. Go
ahead and read.
>> The same was in the beginning with God.
They want you to understand clearly
that it's two. I don't see a third in
here. Do you see a third in here?
But we don't see a single either, do we?
>> No.
>> We see two. Go ahead read.
>> All things were made by him.
>> Go ahead.
>> And without him was not anything made
that was made.
>> Now, who was made Who made everything?
The word.
>> Jesus.
>> How do I know? It was the word made
everything. Skip down to verse 10. Verse
10 and read it.
>> He was in the world, and the world was
made by him, and the world knew him not.
>> And they still don't know him.
All these people going to be in church
tomorrow, they don't know that Jesus was
the one that created everything.
He was. Skip down to verse 13
and go ahead.
>> Which were born out of blood.
>> He wasn't born of blood. Go ahead and
read.
>> Nor of the will of the flesh.
>> Nor of the will of the flesh. Some Some
dude didn't get hot with the sister.
And finish it your head.
>> Nor of the will of man.
>> Nor of the will of man. Go ahead.
>> But of God.
Go ahead and read.
>> And the word was made flesh.
>> And dwelt among us.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And we beheld his glory, the the glory
as the only begotten of the Father, full
of grace and truth.
>> But he's still the only begotten of the
Father.
So he wasn't He wasn't made by the will
of the flesh or by the will of man.
One man and two people came together and
come up with a third one.
He wasn't born of flesh and blood,
either.
Wasn't born of blood, either. He said
flesh, wasn't it?
>> That's what he said.
>> So sisters and brothers, look at this
guy.
How he came into existence.
He is the one that created everything.
And he
had to come and save his creation,
sisters and brothers.
And he came by way of flesh and blood.
Let's go into Hebrews
the second chapter.
For the word was made flesh
and it dwelled among us.
Hebrews chapter 2.
Just letting you know this Bible is
clear, sisters and brothers.
All you got to do is take your time and
read it.
Because you go into Matthew who said
Emmanuel, meaning God with us. That mean
God came with us.
Well, God to then Paul tell you he was
God came forth in the flesh.
>> That's what he said.
>> All of these put together
gives you one clear
vision of what God is doing.
Hebrews 2.
And we're going to start reading at
verse 9.
Hebrews 2
and verse 9. Go ahead and read.
>> But we see Jesus
who was made a little lower than the
angels for the suffering of death.
>> Now, that's why he had to come flesh and
blood. We a little lower than the
angels, we can die. Angels cannot die.
That's why the Lord created the lake of
fire for them, not us.
Cuz he said, "I'm going to punish you
forever being that you live forever."
Go ahead and read.
>> Crowned with glory and honor
>> Uh-huh.
>> that he by the grace of God should taste
death for every man.
>> So, he came that he would die for every
man.
Because God require a sacrifice when
somebody sinned, sisters and brothers.
Skip down to verse 14. Verse 14, go
ahead.
>> For as much then as the children are
partakers of flesh and blood
>> Uh-huh.
>> he also himself likewise took part of
the same.
>> He likewise took part of the same. So,
if you going to take part of something,
that mean you was around before it,
wasn't it?
>> That's right.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> That through death he might destroy him
that had the power of death, that is
the devil.
>> Go ahead.
>> And deliver them who were through fear
of death were all their lifetime subject
to bondage.
>> Now, men don't fear death now because
they don't understand about the second
death.
If they did, it'd be so much cleaning
up, it'd sound like a
towel and soap factory, wouldn't it?
Go ahead and read.
>> 16 For verily he took not on him the
nature of the angels,
>> Uh-huh.
>> but he took on him the seed of Abraham.
>> So, he took on him the seed of Abraham.
Angels can't die, so how's he going to
take on the seed of a angel? Angels
don't have no seed.
>> Mhm.
>> So much for the Nephilims.
>> You brought it up.
>> You understand? This book kill all
falsehood.
But he took upon him the seed of
Abraham. So, why
did he come through Abraham?
Let's go and find out.
Let's go into Genesis chapter 22.
Genesis chapter 22, I'm not taking y'all
too fast, am I?
Okay, all right.
Cuz you've been doing this as long as I
have, you have to kind of check
yourself.
And you have to come out of your own
mind, sister and brother, cuz some of
these things I read it putting that
putting the lesson together.
Do people know this? No, you know it.
Therefore, you got to teach it to the
people so they will know it.
Genesis 22
because the Lord told Abraham that he
was going to have a son, of
>> That's right.
>> Abraham laughed.
Said, "How can me
being 100 years old and my old lady 90
years old going to have a baby?"
God said, "This time
a year this time about this same time of
the year you going to have a baby."
Because Abraham even asked the Lord to
make the covenant through Ishmael.
>> Yeah.
>> He's the father of the Arab system,
brother.
God said, "No, no.
You going to have a son. You going to
name him Isaac.
And he
is the one that my covenant's going to
go through."
>> That's what the book says.
>> So now,
Isaac was born
and God tried Abraham. Sometimes God try
you, sister and brother.
>> Yes, sir.
>> And if you're a true servant of God, you
do the same thing.
Well, you know, God brother told me,
"Well, you know, God knew everything. He
know what you going to do."
Are you sure of that?
If he wanted to know what you were going
to do,
he could. Have you ever thought that
maybe he didn't want to know what you
was going to do?
If he knew what everybody was going to
do, then why is it we going through
this? Cuz he said, "I got this group
over here that's going to do right. I'm
going to save them. And that group over
here I know they're going to be wrong,
so ain't no need of me suffering with
them. Throw them all in the lake of
fire."
Think about what he's saying.
See, the problem is we keep trying to
create God in our image.
Instead of accepting us being created in
his image.
Genesis 22 and verse one. Now he's going
to check Abraham out.
Go ahead and read.
>> And it came to pass afterward, after
these things,
that God did tempt Abraham
and said unto him, "Abraham." And he
said, "Behold,
>> Now, he said, "Abraham."
So, God tempted him.
That mean God has tried him. He didn't
tempt him, he tried him, sisters and
brothers.
Because there was a difference between
tempt and try. Cuz we go in the new book
the Bible and tell you say God don't
tempt nobody with evil, okay?
So, he is trying him.
22 and 1 uh 22 and 2, right?
Read it.
>> And he said, "Take now thy son,
thy only son Isaac,
>> Go ahead.
>> whom thou lovest, and get thee into the
land of Moriah.
>> Now, why did he call Abraham call Isaac
Abraham's only son when Ishmael was his
son and only son?
Because Isaac was a part of the was was
was the one that the covenant came
through.
I tell people all the time, but they
don't want to listen. If you don't uh
are not in the covenant with God, he
don't know you.
He only deal with the people that he
have come to an agreement with.
Now, take care of your son, that only
son,
and do what?
>> Offer him there for a burnt offering
upon one of the mountains which I will
tell thee of.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And Abraham rose up early in the morning
>> Now, let's skip down to verse nine.
>> Okay.
>> And see what Abraham did. Verse nine. Go
ahead and read.
>> And they came to the place where God had
told him of, and Abraham Abraham built
an altar there. Uh-huh. And laid the
wood in order, and bound Isaac his son,
and laid him on the altar upon the wood.
>> So, he built the altar and put Isaac on
his son Isaac had already asked him, "Uh
Father, I see the wood and I I see the
fire.
Where is the sacrifice?"
He said, "God will provide."
>> Mhm.
>> So, he put him on the altar. Go ahead
and read. What verse?
>> 12th verse.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And Abraham stretched forth his hand,
and took the knife to slay his son.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the angel of the Lord called unto
him out of heaven, and said,
>> Uh-huh.
>> "Abraham, Abraham."
>> Go ahead.
>> And he said, "Here am I."
>> And he said, "Lay not thine hand upon
the lad."
>> Go ahead.
>> "Neither do thou anything unto him."
>> "For now I know that thou fears God."
>> WELL, NOW he know that he fears God. Now
he know. WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU,
SISTERS and brothers?
He didn't know. So, how can you dispute
that?
People will argue with you all day, all
night about the same thing. But, they
thinking they're arguing with you.
They're not arguing with you. What are
they arguing with?
>> The Lord.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> "Seeing thou has not withheld thy son,
thine only son from me."
>> Now, I know that you fear me, because
you was going to kill your only son
to please me.
Skip down to verse 15, and go ahead.
>> And the angel of the Lord called unto
Abraham out of heaven the second time,
>> Go ahead.
>> and said, "By myself have I sworn, saith
the Lord, for because thou has done this
thing, and has not withheld thy son,
thine only son,
>> Uh-huh.
>> that in blessing I will bless thee."
>> He said, "By myself I have sworn." So,
he can't swear by nobody greater, can
he? "In blessing I will bless thee." Go
ahead and read.
>> "And in multiplying I will multiply thy
seed as the stars of heaven,
>> Go ahead.
>> and as the sand which is upon the
seashore,
>> Uh-huh.
>> and thy seed shall possess the gate of
his enemies."
>> Now, that's going to happen, sisters and
brothers. We did in the beginning, and
when the Lord come back, he's going to
return Israel.
Person asked me one time, "Well, why Why
is there nobody ever talk about Israel
and returning to the land. I said,
"Because you was told by the Gentile."
He telling you his story.
The Bible's telling you your story.
So, the day going to come when we going
to do that. But then, there's something
greater that happened than that. Go
ahead and read.
>> 18. And in thy seed shall all the
nations of the earth be blessed.
>> And in thy seed shall all of Israel only
be blessed.
>> All the nation.
>> So, who does Who does that include?
>> Everybody.
>> Everybody. So, how you going to cut the
Gentiles off and the strangers off?
You say you're Abraham's seed.
And you And God of Abraham, Isaac, and
Jacob is your God, then how you going to
cut them off? Read that verse to it in
entirety.
>> And in thy seed shall all the nations of
the earth be blessed.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Because thou has obeyed my voice.
>> Go ahead.
>> So, Abraham returned his
>> So, now he said, "In thy seed shall all
nations of the earth be blessed because
thou has obeyed
my voice."
So, now I see
the Jews had to come. The Jesus took on
him the seed of Abraham.
>> Yes, he did.
>> Cuz God told him did he?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Now, let's go into the 9th chapter of
Isaiah.
Isaiah chapter 9.
Hey, sister and brother, people where
you know, at my church. At your church
what?
What did you learn today at your church?
Ask yourself that. That's all I say.
Ask yourself.
What did I learn
at my church?
How many scriptures did my pastor read?
>> Mhm.
>> Being that you if he teaching the word
of God and the word of God is written in
the book, that means somebody should
read some book, don't it?
>> That's right.
>> Isaiah 9.
Isaiah 9 and we're going to start at
verse 7.
Isaiah 9 and 7.
>> What now what verse?
>> Huh?
>> What verse?
>> The Isaiah the 9th chapter and we're
going to I'm sorry, we're going to start
at verse 6.
>> Okay.
>> 9 and 6. Okay, go ahead.
>> For unto us a child is born.
>> Unto us a child is born?
>> Unto us a son is given.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the government shall be upon his
shoulder.
>> And he's going to wrap to you up to
heaven.
>> Mhm.
>> And the government's going to be up on
his shoulder. Go ahead and read.
>> And his name shall be called wonderful.
>> And his name shall be called wonderful?
>> Counselor.
>> Counselor?
>> The mighty God.
>> The mighty God?
>> The everlasting father.
>> The everlasting father?
>> And the prince of peace.
>> And the prince of peace? Oh brother
Bush, you there? They said that Jesus
the father. No, he is our father.
>> Right.
>> Because he adopted our father Jacob and
he changed his name to one of his name,
which is Israel.
He is not the father, he is our father.
Go ahead and read.
>> 7th verse.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Of the increase of his government and
peace, there shall be no end.
>> Of the increase of his government. He
keep talking about government.
>> Yes, sir.
>> That's what ha- that's what you have on
earth.
Nobody talk about government in heaven.
>> Mhm.
>> So why I keep talking about this thing
of of government and increase of
and increase of his government there
shall be no end? Go ahead and read.
>> Upon the throne of David.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And upon his kingdom to order it and to
establish it with judgment and with
justice from henceforth even forever.
>> Now, and he is going this government he
going to govern from on the throne of
David.
And this government is going to be
forever.
So now all we got to go now
and see
who is going to set on the throne of
David.
Let's go into Luke the first chapter.
This is This is so simple, sisters and
brothers.
So simple.
Everybody in here understand this.
If you don't understand this, you left
your mind in the washroom this morning.
Luke chapter 1.
See, we don't We don't do myst-
mysteries here, mysterious stuff. So you
have to depend on the opinion of the
preacher.
You depend on my opinion, you can't get
along across the street, let alone in
King David's kingdom.
You depend on what's written in this
book.
I don't want to be looked upon
as smart.
But I want to be looked upon as a
servant of God.
And looked upon by God. I don't care
what you look upon me as.
Luke 1 and we're going to start at verse
26. Luke 1 and 26.
Okay, go ahead.
>> And in the sixth month the angel Gabriel
was sent from God into city of Galilee
named Nazareth.
>> Go ahead.
>> To a virgin espoused to a man whose name
was Joseph.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Of the house of David.
And the virgin's name was Mary.
>> So, of the house of David and the virgin
name was Mary. The angel God sent
Gabriel cuz this is the angel that that
that is the messenger of God.
>> Yes, sir.
>> He's the one that bring the message and
he ain't God. He's an angel.
But he's the one that everybody think is
God, the Holy Ghost.
>> Yeah.
>> He's an angel.
And once he got to Mary's house,
Joseph's house, what did he say to Mary?
Skip down to verse 30.
Verse 30 and go ahead.
>> And the angel said unto her, "Fear not,
Mary,
for thou hast found favor with God.
>> Go ahead.
>> And behold, thou shalt conceive in thy
womb
>> Uh-huh.
>> and bring forth a son, and shall call
his name Jesus.
>> Now, Jesus came from heaven.
Brother already know there wasn't no J
in this one wasn't no man in the
beginning. You was a pile of day.
The word of the Lord decided to send
from heaven, I'm rolling with it.
>> Yes, sir.
>> And you shall call his name Jesus. Go
ahead and read.
>> He shall be great.
>> And shall be called the son of the
highest.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the Lord God shall give unto him the
throne of his father David.
>> Wait a minute.
When did David go to heaven?
You know, Jesus said in St. John the
third chapter that no man has gone to
heaven.
Except he that came down.
Even the son of man talking about
himself.
So, now if David have not gone to
heaven, how could he have a throne in
heaven?
Think about it, sister and brother.
He going to give him the throne of his
father David. Go ahead and read.
>> And he shall reign over the house of
Jacob forever.
>> Go ahead.
>> And of his kingdom there shall be no
end.
>> And he going to reign over the You mean
the whole house of Jacob went to heaven?
I'm just pointing out the folly that's
being taught in the name of Jesus.
And of his kingdom there shall be no
end. What did Mary say? Go ahead.
>> Then said Mary unto the angel, "How
shall I How shall this be, seeing I know
not a man?"
>> You know the protocol said if a woman
going to have a child, she got to have a
man.
>> Yes, sir.
>> So, how can this be? But what did he
say?
>> And the angel answered and said unto
her, "The Holy Ghost shall come upon
thee, and the power of the highest shall
overshadow thee.
>> Go ahead.
>> Therefore, also that holy thing which
shall be born of thee shall be called
the Son of God."
>> Now, we can't read everything,
but it is written
in Hebrews the 10th chapter where the
Lord said, "Sacrifice and offering thou
wouldst not, but a body has thou
prepared me."
The Lord created a flesh and blood body.
>> Yeah.
>> Jesus took that body over,
and the angel, which is the Holy Spirit,
came and implanted that
in
Mary. It is written in Isaiah.
>> Yes, sir.
>> God has closed me up in my mother's
womb.
All that's written. I can't I can't
teach you all this stuff that's floating
around in my head at one time.
>> Uh-huh.
>> But everything is so simple.
So, what happened?
Angel came,
planted that that body in Israel in
Mary,
and told her he was going to sit on the
throne of David.
David never went to heaven.
>> Hm.
>> And it said his throne is going his
kingdom is going to be forever.
>> Yes, sir.
>> So, we don't see Israel in heaven a
kingdom and a throne and nothing else
now, do we?
So, that means it's got to be in the
future, don't it?
>> Yes, sir.
>> But this man don't understand anything.
They can't understand
that Jesus was God
before he became man, but you understand
it now cuz we just read it, didn't we?
>> Mhm.
>> I want to throw something else in, too.
Let's go into Philippians, the 2nd
chapter.
Philippians chapter 2.
That's why sometime on the
Wednesday night question and answer
where
some questions come in and really
irritates the guest caller.
Because I don't know
what you're trying to do. You're trying
to lay a trap.
And you ain't smart enough to lay no
trap. I tell everybody what about the
question that you ask.
And that guest caller gets irritated
sometime.
Philippians chapter 2.
Philippians chapter 2. We're going to
learn stuff.
See, when you dealing with the truth,
sometime you learns stuff on your way to
learning stuff, sister and brother.
We're going to start at verse
5. And we're going to see how this sound
how this starts out.
Philippians 2 and 5.
Read.
>> Let this mind be in you
>> Let this mind be in you. Who is he
talking to?
Talking to you.
Me and you. Let this mind be in you. Go
ahead and read.
>> Which was also in Christ Jesus.
>> Which was also in Christ Jesus. Go ahead
and read.
>> Who being in the form of God
>> in the form of God
>> thought it not robbery to be equal with
God.
>> WAIT A MINUTE. YOU ASKED TELLING ME
THAT THE DAY GOING TO COME WHEN I will
be equal with God? IS THAT WHAT THEY
SAID?
This man's mind is too small to wrap
around that.
You don't know what God is doing.
But go ahead.
>> Seventh verse.
But made himself of no reputation
>> Uh-huh.
>> and took upon him the form of a servant
>> But he made himself of no reputation and
he took up on him the form of a servant.
Go ahead and read.
>> And was made in the likeness of men.
>> And he was made in the likeness of men.
Who was made
after his own image, wasn't it? Go ahead
and read.
>> And being found in fashion as a man, he
humbled himself and became obedient unto
death, even the death of the cross.
>> So he showed this man by example how you
supposed to obey.
He knew that he had to die.
And he allowed the people that he
created to slap him around, spit on him,
call him names, punch him.
But he obeyed even to death.
You know why? Because he saw the bigger
cause.
Which this man don't see. Go ahead and
read.
>> Wherefore God also hath highly exalted
him and given him a name which is above
every name.
>> So he gave him a name above every name.
Go ahead and read.
>> That at the name of Jesus
>> every knee should bow
>> Every knee should bow. Go ahead and
read.
>> of things in heaven
>> Uh-huh.
>> things in the earth
>> Go ahead.
>> and things under the earth, go ahead,
and that every tongue should confess
that Jesus Christ is the Lord to the
glory of God the Father.
>> And that every tongue should confess
that Jesus Christ is Lord to the glory
of the Father.
Let's see who name that was that's above
every name.
Let's go on to St. John the fifth
chapter.
St. John chapter five.
See, the Bible will tell it all to you.
All you got to do is read it.
>> Yes.
>> A lot of people don't know nothing, then
they say something, you check it with
the book, then they say, "I don't argue
the Bible." Of course you don't argue
because you don't know nothing about it.
You can tell a person they have no no
idea what's written in this book. I
don't argue the Bible.
I tell them I agree. How can you argue
something that you don't know nothing
about?
You ain't never read.
Just like when I was dealing with
talking about something when I used to
go to prison ministry. A guy asked me,
"Well, I said something out of out of
the Quran.
Uh brother, have you ever read the
Quran?"
No. Well, then how can you say something
out of it? I said, "I agree with you."
I went and bought a whole Quran and read
it in one week.
I went back and whooped his head with
his own book.
How can I do that? Because I read it.
Don't you know Jesus is in the Holy
Quran just as much as he's in this Bible
here?
People don't know that.
St. John five
and verse 39. Five and 39. Read it.
>> Search the scriptures.
>> Search the scripture?
>> For in them you think you have eternal
life.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And they are they which testify of me.
>> Now, people don't understand that.
That's testifying of Jesus. But skip
down to verse 43 and go ahead.
>> I am come in my father's name.
>> I'm come in whose name?
Go ahead.
>> And you receive me not.
>> Uh-huh.
>> If another shall come in his own name,
him will you receive.
>> He said, "But if another come in his own
name, him will you will receive." John
the Baptist came in the spirit of
Elijah.
But he come in his own name.
And the people received him.
So, if Jesus come
in the father's name,
what was his name before he came?
Let's find out.
Let's go into Exodus the sixth chapter.
Ain't no mystery. They always talk about
the mystery of the of the gospel. Ain't
no mystery. It's a mystery to you
because you didn't read.
How God's going to put your behavior
Let your behavior dictate whether you're
going to go to lake of fire or not.
And he's going to give you something so
mysterious that you can't read it. You
can't understand. Uh-uh.
No, no.
Exodus chapter six.
And we're going to read start reading at
verse two.
Exodus chapter six.
And verse two.
Read it.
>> And God speaketh unto Moses and said
unto them,
>> Go ahead.
>> I am the Lord.
>> I am the Lord. Go ahead and read.
>> And I appeared unto Abraham and unto
Isaac and unto Jacob by the name of God
Almighty.
>> And I appeared unto Abraham, Isaac, and
Jacob by the name of God Almighty. Go
ahead and read.
>> But by my name Jehovah
>> But by what?
>> By my name Jehovah
>> was I not known to them.
>> Don't you know that people still telling
you that JEHOVAH IS THE FATHER?
THAT WAS JESUS' NAME. He
is Jehovah.
>> Yes.
>> But he didn't come in his own name as
Jehovah. He came in his Father's name.
That mean that the Father's name was
Jesus.
That's why it had to be sent from
heaven. Who wouldn't have known the
Father's name if he didn't send it down?
>> Nobody.
>> It's so simple, isn't it?
That's why I said, I gave him a name
above every name. He didn't give him a
name above him. He gave him his name.
That at the name of Jesus, which was
him, every knee shall bow, and every
tongue shall confess to the glory of the
Father, because that's the Father's
name.
It's all laid out, sisters and brothers.
Ain't no mystery about this.
Let me show you something. Let's go into
Isaiah
the 12th chapter.
Got to love this this book, sisters and
brothers. I love this word of God,
because it's so clear.
Let's you know where you came from and
where you're going.
All you got to do is read it.
>> Yes, sir.
>> It's so clear.
Isaiah
chapter 12, and we're going to read one
verse.
Verse two.
Isaiah chapter 12
and verse
two.
Reading.
>> Behold, God is my salvation.
>> Behold, God is my salvation. Go ahead.
>> I will trust
>> Uh-huh.
>> and not be afraid.
>> I will trust and not be afraid. Go
ahead.
>> For the Lord Jehovah
>> is my strength
>> Is my strength?
>> and my song
>> And my
what?
>> song
>> And my song. Go ahead.
>> He also is become my salvation.
He created this man. Man committed
suicide in the Garden of Eden. So, the
Lord had to come and save him. That's
where salvation come from.
One that is to be saved.
He's my strength and my song. The Lord
God Jehovah is.
>> That's right.
>> But now, he is become my salvation.
So, we're going to see
whose name
comes under salvation.
Let's go into Acts, the fourth chapter.
You see, one little verse like that tell
a whole lot when you have read all the
scriptures around it.
That's why I tell people read for
yourself.
I'm going to teach you everything that's
written in this book that I understand,
but read for yourself so you can
understand.
Acts chapter four.
See, here where Peter and them
had to
heal a man.
You know, and the Pharisees and all of
that, they didn't like it because
he healed him in the wrong name.
So, what they did was they come up on
them. And let's see what they said.
Acts four and 2. Acts chapter 4 and
we're going to start reading at verse 1,
brother. Acts chapter 4 and verse 1.
Read it.
>> And as they spake unto the people, the
priests and the captain of the temple
and the Sadducees came upon him.
>> Now look, sisters and brothers. You know
all the time that the apostles and the
prophets
approach y'all salted, it's always from
the religious people.
Do you think that's changed?
Go up and run them Sunday CHURCHES AND
SAY, "CHRIST was not born on the 25th
day of December."
What they going to say to you?
>> Get him.
>> You ain't going to heaven. God's coming
here. Ooh, here's he. Please get him out
of here.
The regular street person would say, uh
You What were you saying that he wasn't
born on the 25th day of December? Can
you show me that?
Then you can show him.
But that Sunday Christian
Roman Christian
will assault you if you keep on.
What verse?
>> Second verse.
>> Go ahead.
>> Being grieved that they taught the
people and preached through Jesus the
resurrection from the dead.
>> Then these religious people was grieved
because Peter and them was teaching
these people about Jesus and about the
resurrection.
They was grieved. How can you be grieved
with that?
Then they put them in jail and they let
them out.
And they went back and said, "Go Get on
back out there and keep talking this
book." Skip down to verse 7. Verse 7, go
ahead.
>> And when they had set them in the midst,
they asked
>> Now the Pharisee Well, they found them.
They grabbed them again and they set
them in the midst, and they did what?
>> They asked, "By what power or by what
name have you done this?"
>> By what power and by what name have you
done this? They already knew. They were
mad because he was doing it in the name
of Jesus. Go ahead and read.
>> Then Peter, filled with the Holy Ghost,
said unto them,
>> Go ahead.
>> "Ye rulers of the people, and elders of
Israel,
if we this day be examined of the good
deed done unto this poor man, by what
means is he made whole?"
>> Now, look. Look, if we being examined
by
the religious hierarchy of these days
because we healed this man,
then what are we dealing What are we
talking about here?
That's what they're being examined by.
What verse are we?
>> 10.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> Be it known unto you all,
>> Be it known. We'll let you know it ain't
us. It's not our power.
Be it known unto all. Go ahead and read.
>> and to all the people of Israel,
>> Uh-huh.
>> that by the name of Jesus Christ of
Nazareth,
>> But by the name of Jesus Christ, which
come from Nazareth. Go ahead and read.
>> whom you crucified, whom God raised from
the dead,
>> whom y'all crucified. That's why they
were upset. The religious people killed
him.
And God raised him from the dead. Go
ahead and read.
>> Even by him do up this man stand here
before you all.
>> So, it's by the name of Jesus that this
man is standing before us. He You
healed.
Not us.
The name of Jesus. Skip down to verse 12
and read it.
>> Neither is there salvation in any other
>> Neither is there salvation in any other.
Go ahead and read.
>> For there is none other name under
heaven
>> For there's none other name under heaven
>> given among men,
>> whereby we must be saved.
>> whereby we must be safe.
That's why I told you in Isaiah 12,
the Lord God Jehovah
is my strength.
>> Is has become
our salvation.
>> And now he has become my salvation.
Because he left the name Jehovah,
but he came in the name of Jesus, but he
was the same person.
>> Yeshua.
>> This is too simple.
That's what happen when you read the
book.
And everybody
kicking Hebrew kicking about name of
Jesus, Yeshua.
Yeshua.
Yacua.
Yahuda.
We going to see what the Lord say.
His name is going to be called.
Let's go into Malachi the first chapter.
Malachi
chapter 1.
That's why I've got a couple of letters.
I didn't even answer.
Why should we sit down and try to talk
some and we are
we don't speak the same language.
Well, you know, we
we speak English, that don't mean you
speak the same language.
>> That's right.
>> Malachi chapter 1.
And we going to read verse 6 first.
Malachi 1 and 6. We're going to read
half of six. That's all what I'm looking
for.
1 and 6. Go ahead and read.
>> As a son honors his father
>> He said as a son honors his father, go
ahead.
>> and a servant his master
>> and a servant his master, go ahead.
>> If then I be a father
>> If I be a father
>> where is mine honor?
>> Where is mine honor?
>> And if I be a master
>> Uh-huh.
>> where is my fear?
>> If I be a master, where is my fear?
What?
>> Saith the Lord of hosts.
>> Go ahead.
>> unto you, oh priests
>> unto you, oh priests of God. Who is the
one that the Lord chose to chose to be
priests to all the sons of Adam?
>> Israel
>> He's talking to Israel here. Unto you,
oh priests, that what?
>> that despise my name
>> that despise my name.
When you go around these Hebrews and you
use the word Jesus, don't they start
tripping?
>> Yes.
>> He says, "Oh, priests despise his name."
The one that's SUPPOSED TO BE SPREADING
HIS NAME.
Get down to verse 11 now and see what he
said. Verse 11, go ahead.
>> For from the rising of the sun
>> From from the rising of the sun
>> even to the going down of the same
>> even to the going down of the same. Go
ahead and read.
>> My name shall be great among the
Gentiles.
>> Wait a minute. My name going to be great
among the Gentiles. Gentiles, these are
European what we call WHITE FOLKS.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHAT is the greatest name among white
folks?
>> Jesus.
>> Jesus said the book said my name, didn't
it?
Go ahead and read.
>> And even in every place
incense shall be offered unto my name.
>> Go ahead.
>> a pure offering
>> Uh-huh.
>> For my name shall be great among the
even
>> Uh-huh.
>> saith the Lord of hosts.
>> Now, who are what heathen mean the
nations?
>> That's right.
>> What is the greatest name among the
nations?
>> Jesus.
>> I had never heard of Amar'e Stoudemire
until I worked for him.
I remember
years ago when uh
we had this you know we got this brother
Amar'e Stoudemire, professional
basketball player.
His manager called here
because he was a friend of God to go to
the Memphis class
and said, "Brother Boy, uh uh uh
uh
will you uh
come to New York
because
Brother Stoudemire is about to become uh
uh
a joiner to uh uh become Jew- uh join
Judaism."
Now, first thing he asked me, "Could you
come to New York
cuz I want you to talk to Brother
Stoudemire."
I said, "Hey, Stoudemire ain't like
everybody else. He got my money. Let him
buy a ticket and come before me.
I'll teach him here and set in class."
But he only reason I asked Brother
Brother Boo because he about to join
student Judaism. I said, "Get me a
ticket."
And when I went there you had these
little Hebrews sitting around, a group
of them.
They can't stop him from joining
Judaism.
But when I mentioned Jesus
the leader said, "Well, you know, I
don't know about that name, man, you
know." I said, "Is that right?"
I took him to Malachi and read verse 11
to him. You know what he did?
He got up
and left the room.
He's gone for about a half hour or 45
minutes.
And I was eating his servants alive
while he was gone.
So, we got to baptize Stahli my and his
mother.
Because this written in Old Testament,
ain't it?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Not the New Testament. That's what
called him.
I said, "What's the greatest man among
the Gentiles that are white folks?" He
didn't say nothing. He just got up and
walked out of the room.
Cuz he knew he was done.
Stick a fork in him.
What?
What else did the Lord say about his
priest? Let's go into Malachi, the
second chapter.
And verse one.
Malachi two
and one. Okay, go ahead.
>> And now,
O ye priest, this commandment is for
you.
>> Talking to strictly to Israel. Go ahead
and read.
>> If you will not hear,
>> if you will not lay it to heart,
>> If you will not lay it to heart,
>> to give glory unto my name,
>> To give glory unto my name, Peter them
got beat
for using that name.
Brother them well, you know, you don't
know what Peter them spoke. I said,
"I'll tell you what, whatever you spoke,
he still got beat for using the name."
>> So.
>> Because of that, what he say?
>> Saith the Lord of hosts, I will even
send a curse upon you, and I will curse
your blessings. Yea, I have cursed them
already because you laid not to heart.
>> Hey, look at us now.
Everybody done took Christianity away
from you and you're the original
Christian.
Then took your land away from you.
And you
were the original inhabitants of Israel.
I can't took everything from you.
You know why? Because the Lord said
because you won't acknowledge my name,
I'm going to lay a curse on you. That
was written before Jesus came in the
flesh.
The Lord knew what these people going to
do, sisters and brothers?
He knew.
So, sisters and brothers,
the name of Jesus
is the only name given under the sun
whereby men might be saved.
And you know what I'm going to tell you,
sisters and brothers?
People still don't know it.
They just don't know.
It is said that uh
that people in heaven
Ain't nobody in heaven. We can show you
that.
And anybody that tell you
that somebody is in heaven
still
don't know him. Therefore, he is unknown
to them.
Ain't nobody in heaven.
Then some mess they say.
That somebody is burning in hell.
These people have dug through this earth
all kind of ways and they never run into
the liquid fire.
The Lord told you when he was going to
reward you. Let's go into Isaiah, the
40th chapter. He let you know when you
going to get what he promised you.
Isaiah chapter 40.
What I'm saying, sisters and brothers,
people just sit down and listen to stuff
that simply don't make sense.
You'll get a rebellious thing and you're
going to rebel against God. God going to
throw him out of heaven and then give
him a domain.
So, he can cook you in the fire.
He made the fire to cook him.
But, being that he's telling the story,
so he changed it on you.
Isaiah 40.
And we're going to start at verse 9.
Isaiah 40
and verse 9.
Okay.
Go ahead.
>> Zion
that bringeth good tidings, get thee
into the high mountain.
O Jerusalem, that bringeth good tidings,
lift up thy voice with strength.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Lift it up, be not afraid. Say unto the
cities of Judah, "Behold your God."
>> Behold your God. Go ahead and read.
>> Behold, the Lord God will come with
strong hand.
>> The Lord God will come with the strong
hand. Go ahead and read.
>> And his arm shall rule for him.
>> And his arm shall arm shall rule for
him. Go ahead.
>> Behold, his reward is with him.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And his work before him.
>> Behold, his reward is with him.
And his work before him.
So, if the reward is with him, how can
you get it before he come?
Let's go on. And John going to verify
that in Revelation, the 22nd chapter.
Revelation chapter 22.
Somebody tell you, you know, you call
call me and look here brother boy can
uh
can you loan me $10?
Yeah, I can loan you $10.
And I'm on the west side and you're on
the east side of Chicago.
How you going to get it until I come?
>> I can't get it.
>> Okay, man, when I get over there I'm
going to give it to you.
But we don't understand simple stuff
like that.
We've done been in these churches and
been educated.
Revelation 22 and we're going to read
one verse.
Verse 12.
Revelation 22
and verse 12.
22 and 12.
Okay, read it.
>> And behold, I come quickly.
>> And behold, I come quickly. Go ahead and
read.
>> And my reward is with me.
>> And my reward is with me?
>> To give every man according as his work
shall be.
>> Now, look. If your work got you in
heaven, you can't get it until he come.
And that is so clear.
But in case you can't understand real
simple and clear stuff,
I'm going to read something else to you.
Let's go to 1 Corinthians the 15th
chapter.
1 Corinthians chapter 15
and we're going to start reading
at verse 21.
1 Corinthians 15
we're going to start at verse 21.
I'm telling you this is simple stuff
here.
If I'm going to give you $10 and and I
tell you well
I I I
uh
I'm going to give it to you when I come.
Oh, brother boy, you didn't promise me
$10. It is in my pocket now.
How did it get there?
Don't make sense.
Verse 21, go ahead.
>> For since by man came death,
by man came also the resurrection of the
dead.
>> Since by man came death, by man came
also the resurrection of the dead, go
ahead and read.
>> For as in Adam all die,
>> as in Adam all die,
>> even so in Christ shall all be made
alive.
>> So, in Jesus, he through him everybody's
going to be made alive. That's what
scares me. It said all be made alive,
even the people that's going to go to
the lake of fire.
That scares me. I just wish he'd let me
keep sleeping if I don't make the cut.
But, go ahead and read.
>> 23.
But, every man in his own order.
>> But, every man in his own order, go
ahead and read.
>> Christ the first fruit,
>> afterward
>> afterwards,
>> they that are Christ at his coming.
>> They that are Christ at his coming. Is
he here?
So, then where are the dead?
>> In the grave.
>> All of them.
That's not hard to understand, is it?
Well, you know, uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
uh uh uh uh uh
My mother's in heaven. Is that right?
But, this says she ain't
If heaven is a reward, why is she there
and she can't get in till the Lord come?
Sisters and brothers, all you got to do
is read
this
book.
That's all you got to do.
So, when Moses came, they told me the
law the law Moses ain't got no law.
Jesus is the one that sent Moses,
sisters and brothers.
He is the one that sent Moses.
Let me show you what happened when he
sent Moses, when he got rid of sin.
Let's go into Exodus
the third chapter. And I got two more
places after this.
Exodus chapter 3.
All right, you know, I don't want to do
law Moses. We ain't under the law. Look
here, Moses ain't got no law.
Exodus chapter 3.
And we're going to start at verse
13.
Exodus 3
and verse
13.
Exodus 3
and 13.
Okay, read it.
>> And Moses said unto God,
behold,
when I come unto the children of Israel
and say unto them, "The God of your
fathers have sent me unto you." And they
shall say to me, "What is his name?
What shall I say unto them?"
>> Now, that's a reasonable question.
Cuz when I go and tell them that God
sent me, they're going to ask me his
name. Look what he said to him. Go ahead
and read.
>> And God said unto Moses,
>> Uh-huh.
>> I am that I am.
Go ahead.
>> And he said, "Thus shall thou say unto
the children of Israel,
>> Go ahead.
>> I am have sent me unto you."
>> I am have sent me unto you.
So, let you and let you I'm going to let
you know now who this is talking about.
That told Moses that.
Let's go to St. John 8th chapter.
St. John chapter 8.
And we're going to start at verse 56.
St. John 8.
And 56. This is Jesus talking to the
Jews now.
The Pharisees. Look what he said. 8 and
56. St. John 8.
And chapter 56.
Okay, read it.
>> Your father Abraham rejoiced to see my
day.
>> So, your father Abraham rejoiced to see
my day. Go ahead.
>> And he saw it and was glad.
>> And he saw it and he was glad. Now, what
did you say to him? Go ahead.
>> Then said the Jews unto him, Thou art
not yet 50 years old.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And hast thou seen Abraham?
>> Yeah, man. You ain't 50 years old. You
going to tell us you seen Abraham? Go
ahead and read.
>> Jesus said unto them, Verily, verily, I
say unto you,
>> Uh-huh.
>> Before Abraham was, I am.
>> Same one. Let you know who was talking
to Moses, wasn't it?
Before Abraham was,
I am.
And you got people around here called on
the name of Jesus.
And they said, I know the Lord. I got a
personal
relationship with it.
And then you turn around say, "Okay,
then you keep the commandment. You ain't
got to keep them old commandments. They
was nailed to the cross."
You know what they just told me when
they say stuff like that?
That he is still unknown to them.
>> Yes.
>> And let me show you what they's talking
about. This is last place.
Let's go to 1 John the 2nd chapter.
>> Ooh.
>> 1 John chapter 2.
People have Well, I know the Lord. Ask
him, "Do you have to keep the
commandment?" No.
Then you you make a note of this and
carry it around in your pocket and in
your purse.
1 John chapter 2.
And we're going to start reading at
verse one.
St. John chapter 2 and verse one.
Like I said,
carry this around on a little piece of
paper.
St. John 2
and verse one. Two and one.
Okay, read it.
>> My little children,
these things I write unto you that you
sin not.
>> If my little children, these things that
I write unto you that you sin not, go
ahead and read.
>> And if any man sin,
>> Uh-huh.
>> we have an advocate with the Father,
>> Go ahead.
>> Jesus Christ the righteous.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And he is the propitiation for our sins.
>> Now, if any man sin, then we have a
advocate. We have somebody to plead our
cause if we repent if we repent.
For he is the sacrifice for our sins. Go
ahead and read.
>> And not for ours only,
>> Uh-huh.
>> but also for the sins of the whole
world.
>> Go ahead.
>> And hereby we do know that we know him.
>> Hereby we do know that we know him.
What?
>> If we keep his commandments.
But keep reading.
>> He that saith I know him
>> and keepeth not his commandments
>> is a liar
>> and the truth is not in it.
>> And the truth is not in it.
So if you want TO CHECK SOMEBODY OUT TO
see if
Jesus is still unknown to them, ask
them, do you have to keep the
commandments? No. Okay, have a good day.
End of story.
Thank you for your time.